// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the name of the young boy in this story?",
    answer: "Wandile",
    options: [
      "Khulani",
      "Troy",
      "Wandile",
      "Simo"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What did Wandile enjoy looking at during the night?",
    answer: "The stars and moon in the night sky",
    options: [
      "The sun in the night sky",
      "The stars and moon in the night sky",
      "The sun in the day sky",
      "The stars and moon in the day sky"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Did Wandile's mother know about his son's love for exploring the sky?",
    answer: "Yes she did",
    options: [
      "Yes she did",
      "No she did not know",
      "She did not care about it",
      "She ignored that"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What did Wandile's mother by him as a suprise?",
    answer: "A Telescope",
    options: [
      "A digital camera",
      "A car toy",
      "A cellphone",
      "A Telescope"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "A Telescope is a tool for?",
    answer: "For seing faraway objects",
    options: [
      "For seing nearby objects",
      "For seing faraway objects",
      "For seing new objects",
      "For seing invisible objects"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "How many planets does our solar system has?",
    answer: "9 planets",
    options: [
      "12 planets",
      "10 planets",
      "6 planets",
      "9 planets"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Planet Earth has how may moons?",
    answer: "1 moon",
    options: [
      "2 moons",
      "1 moon",
      "3 moons",
      "9 moons"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which order of planets is correct for our solar system?",
    answer: "1.Mercury 2.Venus 3.Earth 4.Mars 5.Jupiter 6.Saturn 7.Uranus 8.Neptune 9.Pluto",
    options: [
      "1.Mercury 2.Venus 3.Earth 4.Mars 5.Jupiter 6.Saturn 7.Uranus 8.Neptune 9.Pluto",
      "1.Earth 2.Mars 3.Jupiter 4.Saturn 5.Uranus 6.Neptune 7.Mercury 8.Venus 9.Pluto",
      "1.Neptune 2.Pluto 3.Mercury 4.Venus 5.Earth 6.Mars 7.Jupiter 8.Saturn 9.Uranus",
      "1.Jupiter 2.Saturn 3.Uranus 4.Neptune 5.Pluto 6.Mercury 7.Venus 8.Earth 9.Mars"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Planet Earth our home it the...?",
    answer: "Is the 3rd plannet on the solar system orbit",
    options: [
      "Is the 5th plannet on the solar system orbit",
      "Is the 4th plannet on the solar system orbit",
      "Is the 2nd plannet on the solar system orbit",
      "Is the 3rd plannet on the solar system orbit"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 10,
    question: "How did Wandile feel about his new Telescope?",
    answer: "He was very happy and wanted to use it right away",
    options: [
      "He was very sad and wanted to break right away",
      "He was very happy and wanted to use it right away",
      "He was very angry because it is not what he wanted",
      "He was mad at his mother and he cried"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];
